"Previously on The Mentalist..."
- "He says his name is Patrick Jane."
- Never met him.
- Did he say why he came in?
- Just that he wants to talk to you.
Mr. Jane!
"Teresa Lisbon, it's nice to meet you."
We always thought that you and Lisbon
would, you know, get together.
Jane and Lisbon, yeah right.
- And voila.
- So you're gonna build us a house?
- It's a start.
- I need to know
- that you're committed to this, to us.
- I am.
Then are you gonna take off
your wedding ring?
I have a guy who's saying things
about the murders.
- Well, what is he saying Wylie?
- He's a psychic.
I saw that the killer's gonna
kill again, tonight.
"Why would the killer care
if Gabriel was a real psychic?"
"He wants one for some reason
and Gabriel didn't pass the test."
"Welcome back to Austin Today.
I'm Dan Glover."
"And with me is Patrick Jane,
a psychic who works with the FBI."
I'm just trying to help my colleagues
understand this man.
- "How would you describe him?"
- "I would say that he's obviously angry"
"probably in a lot of pain."
Lazarus. Interesting name.
- "He rose from the dead."
- So I hear.
I saw you on TV.
You said you know things.
He's in there.
Jane... Hey.
Can you stand up?
- You Agent Tork?
- Yeah.
You guys done looking around in there?
'Cause we're just sitting
on our hands out here.
There's nothing we could find.
It's a mess in there.
But the structure's sound.
Your people can go in. Have fun.
Thanks.
All right, listen up.
It's been reported there are two bodies
in the basement of this house.
There may also be evidence
pertaining to as many as 10 homicides
committed by the recently deceased
individual known as Lazarus.
Real name Joseph Keller.
We wanna put these cases to bed
so that means break out
the fine-toothed combs.
Let's go.
How's your head?
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
It's fine.
Ears are still ringing a little
but, uh...
just getting ready for the remodel.
- I brought sandwiches.
- Those are the magic words.
Come with me.
Is it me, or does it seem like
the house slants a little bit to the left?
Optical illusion.
You're not wearing
your wedding ring.
I'm not married.
The ground is slanty,
so it makes the structure
look like it's leaning,
but it is, in fact, not.
It's just an optical illusion.
- Slanty, huh?
- Yeah.
Technical term.
This ring has been with me
for a very long time, and, uh...
it has obvious significance
with my past.
It also represents...
meeting you.
If I didn't have this ring,
I would never have met you.
So in a sense, uh...
it has the potential to represent
my future, as well.
And I-I'm not expecting
you would ever wear it, but...
I wanna share it with you
and...
I want it to represent our future...
together.
I want you to be my wife.
Will you marry me?
Okay.
- Yes, yes.
- Yes?
Excellent.
I'm glad that's dealt with.
I was a little nervous.
Oh, come on. You knew
I was gonna say yes.
No, even after all these years,
you're still a mystery to me.
- I am?
- Thank you.
Hey, guys, how's the Lazarus case going?
Keller's house is being processed
right now.
Tork's on the scene.
We're just squaring away the paperwork.
Oh, good. Good, good, good.
All right.
Do you guys need anything? Can I help?
Mm... No, not really.
Look, you know, old job's over.
New job hasn't begun. You know,
I'm just spinning my wheels here.
- Hey.
- Hey, guys.
So, um... we wanted you
to be the first to know.
Um... yeah.
We're getting married.
Hey!
- I told you.
- No, you didn't.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, man!
- That's wonderful.
- That's awesome.
- Thank you.
- When's the big day?
Eh, no big day.
I don't want any wedding fuss.
Oh, we're just gonna slip away quietly
in the next couple of days.
All right.
"It's not unusual to be loved
by anyone"
"it's not unusual to have fun
with anyone"
"But when I see you
hanging around with anyone"
"It's not unusual to see me cry"
"I wanna die"
- "Hi. How are you?"
- "Good. How are you?"
"Good."
"But when I see you out
and about, it's such a crime"
"If you should ever wanna be
loved by anyone"
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
"It's not unusual, it happens every day"
Oh, my lord. Sir?
I'm good.
That darn barbecue, I swear.
These are two for one, right?
- "Hey-hey! Hey!"
- "That's awesome!"
"Hey, even this guy's happy
about it, right?"
"Yeah, congrats."
- Oh, hi! Hey!
- "Hey."
- "Congratulations!"
- "Somebody went number two."
- Thanks.
- "Yeah. All right."
"So, anyway, did you tell uh--
did you tell Tommy yet?"
Eh, he's chasing a bail jumper
in Alaska.
I left him a message.
"Eh, well, you snooze, you lose."
"We're gonna miss him
at the bachelor party, though."
There is no bachelor party.
We're getting married
the day after tomorrow
just me and Jane
and the Justice of the Peace.
No big wedding, no guests.
"But... family, right?"
- "Yeah, family."
- "Yeah."
No, it's just us.
We wanna get married quietly.
"Well, so, we'll be quiet.
But we're gonna be there, T."
- "I mean, no argument."
- "Hey, Stan, hold it."
"It's her deal, her choice.
You know, she wants to do it that way"
- "then let her do it."
- "What are you saying, you mook?"
Guys, come on!
"If we're not there, Mom's gonna spin
in her grave"
- "like a freaking crankshaft."
- "Oh, my God."
"She'll be crying for shame
that our sister, our only sister--"
"Oh, would you can it, please, Stan?
Teresa just said she don't us there."
"Why would you wanna be there
if she doesn't want us there?"
- "I mean--"
- "You're a sad, bitter man, Jimmy Lisbon."
- "Well, I-I smile through it."
- "Don't you ever--"
- "I smile through the sadness."
- "Stop it. He's doing it again."
- "I got stronger, though."
- "Ever since he was a little kid--"
- "It's just-- it cuts to the airflow!"
- "Yeah."
- Don't worry.
- Don't worry about what?
You're worried that I'm gonna be upset
because you invited your brothers
to our marriage.
- How did you know that?
- When we're married
do you think you might stop
asking that question?
- It's okay, isn't it?
- They're family.
Thank you. It means a lot to them.
Of course.
Since my brothers are coming
it feels funny
not to invite just a couple
of members from the team.
No, no. You know what? You're right.
We should keep it small.
Small. Just my brothers.
Eh, fine. Invite away.
We're gonna need a few more guests
just to dilute the alcohol content.
- Thank you.
- Just three or four, though.
Where do we draw the line?
Well, that's why we decided
not to invite anyone.
I know. I know. I'm sorry. It's just--
here we are.
- Here we are.
- What?
Oh, look, I'm just gonna surrender
to fate, all right?
So be it.
Big, huge, massive wedding.
No, just 8 or 9 very close friends
at the courthouse-- 9 or 10
and then we can go
to O'Malley's bar afterwards.
12 tops.
Or we could go to a restaurant.
No big deal.
It's not like we're hiring a caterer.
- We don't have a gift registry or anything.
- Sure. Okay.
- Where are you going?
- Well, I have to get you a ring.
- I already have one.
- That is for us.
You need one for you.
- I do?
- You do.
All right, well, shouldn't I come
with you?
Isn't that how you're supposed
to do it?
No, I think we'll waste time bickering.
Besides, I have better taste.
- You think you do.
- You'll see.
- N-nothing too gauche.
- Bye!
- Hey, boss.
- Hey.
The less I have to do,
the more coffee I drink.
So, do you and Lena wanna come
and watch us get married?
Oh. Uh, Lena went to
a trade conference in Prague
but, uh, you know, I'd be honored.
I thought you guys
weren't having any guests.
Well, we kind of changed our minds.
It's just gonna be a few people--
a dozen, 15.
All right. I'm there.
Where and when?
We don't know yet.
It's nothing fancy.
Oh, well, you have to have it
at our house. I insist.
We have the perfect spot
for a casual wedding.
Really?
I'd be thrilled.
That is so nice of you.
- What's up?
- Some surprise, huh?
I didn't see the wedding thing coming.
It wasn't that hard to guess.
- Something on your mind?
- No.
Actually, yes.
Someone might get in touch with you
about me requesting a transfer.
I just wanted you to hear it
from me first.
- A transfer where?
- Salt Lake.
Office there is starting
a cyber-crime initiative.
They're looking for people.
It's desk work,
but it's more my speed, I think.
Uh, let's face it, I didn't do that well
when we were going after Keller.
It's not easy being in the bullpen.
Michelle's desk is right there, and...
Anyway, I think a change of pace
would be good.
Plus, you're gonna be rebuilding
the team.
This'll pretty much
give you a blank slate.
- Come here.
- What?
Come here.
- Stop feeling sorry for yourself.
- No, I'm not.
You are.
You made some mistakes going
after Keller? Welcome to the club.
I bat 300 on a good day.
You miss Vega.
Now remember who she was.
She'd never run away from a challenge
like this and neither should you.
And you're right.
I have to rebuild the team and I wanna
start with people that I know and trust.
- So stick around.
- Or what, you'll hit me again?
I'm asking you to stay, Wylie.
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
Check in with Tork.
I wanna know what's going on
at the house.
Sure. And Cho...
- Thanks.
- No problem.
This is the ring we sent you
a picture of.
It was my grandmother's.
Anne's dad gave it
to me to propose with.
Which is sweet, but it's not
really me, you know?
So we thought maybe we could
take the diamond out
put it in a necklace or something.
Of course. Uh, may I--
may I see it?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, let me get my loupe.
We'll just need to take
a closer look at the stone.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm helping another customer
right now, sir.
FBI--
give 'em back their ring right now
or I will be forced to shoot you.
Don't worry. Just kidding.
I don't even carry a real gun.
I have a lotta close friends
that do, though.
- What's happening?
- All will be revealed.
- Their ring is in your right hand.
- Uh, sir, you've made a mistake.
- We've got the ring right here.
- Uh, that's a replica.
A... replica?
He did a French drop to swap
the valuable ring with a cheap replica.
French drop is a sleight-of-hand move.
Not important.
That ring never belonged
to your grandmother
and it's not a real diamond.
- Is that true?
- Of course not.
He would study the ring
that he just gave you
then break the sad news that
your grandma's ring is a phony
and you'd be none the wiser.
This is insane.
Then you won't mind opening up
your right hand, will you?
Open up your right hand, please, sir.
Holy moly.
Well, thank you for your assistance, folks.
I'll take it from here.
Don't worry, ma'am.
The real ring is in your hand.
- Good day to you.
- Thank you.
My pleasure.
So, my crooked friend,
today is your lucky day.
- Is it?
- Well, on a normal day
you'd be off to the pokey now
but as it happens...
I'm in the market for a diamond ring.
So show me
your very best selection, please.
And, sir, if I see any glass...
the cuffs will come out.
Nothing too gauche.
What's up?
Tork just called in from the crime scene.
No intact corpses in the basement
but a lotta body parts,
badly burned and fragmented.
Have them rush the DNA tests.
Pull some strings if you have to.
Why the rush?
Still got a lotta media interest.
The bosses wanna be able
to announce we got the guy.
For that, we need a coroner's report,
so let's get on it.
Okay, right away.
- Hey, did Abbott give you the news?
- Hey.
We're having a real wedding
at his house.
- He did.
- You're gonna be there, right?
Of course.
I could use your help with something
if you're not too busy.
What's that?
What do you think?
Makes you look short.
Snow cone.
Slutty elf.
You want a simple piece
with clean lines
maybe something vintage
and off-white.
What he said.
Thank you for doing this.
I asked you along
'cause I thought you'd be honest.
I had no idea you were such
a fashion expert.
Not me.
My mom could run up
a designer gown before breakfast.
- Cut her cloth by eye.
- Cool.
My mom had a sewing machine,
but it was always in hock.
She'd be very proud of you.
Looking like this?
Very proud.
Thank you, Kimball.
All right, good night, Wade.
And, uh, tell Shaniqua
I said thanks for the fan mail.
Excuse me.
I-I don't have any change, man.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Here, look. You can take it.
You can take it. Here.
Get in the car.
Do as I say and you won't get hurt.
Stop the vehicle.
"Very slowly. No one gets hurt."
Put the car in park and get out.
Easy.
Give me your phone.
All right.
No problems.
What's the passcode?
There isn't any.
Wallet.
Look, uh, I only got
about 20 bucks in it.
And, uh...
Would you let me keep
my driver's license?
I-I don't wanna have to go
to the DMV.
Sure.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thank you.
No! No! No!
- Tork.
- Patrick Jane, please.
Um, sorry. He's not in.
This is Dan Glover
from Austin Today.
I interviewed Jane recently
about this whole Lazarus case.
Sure. I remember you.
I just wanna do a quick follow-up.
Is he available?
I'm afraid, uh, you're gonna have
to wait a few days on that.
He's outta the office for a while.
Can you tell me where I can find him?
It'll only take a few moments.
I'd say he's pretty unfindable
at the moment.
"He's getting married in a few days."
- Married?
- Yeah.
I can, uh, take a message,
tell him you called.
No, no need.
Okey-doke.
Huh.
If I just remembered how tedious
this aspect of the marriage is
I might not have asked you.
No, seriously. I'm only on page two.
You know, I could just give you
the ring and we could elope.
Don't be mean. No take-backs.
I could give you this
and we could be in Fiji by nightfall.
There are people coming.
We're getting married, damn it.
- Suit yourself.
- You got a ring?
Yes, I did.
- You gonna show it to me?
- You wanna see it?
Show me.
I'll take this,
and you'll fill all of this out.
Oh, my God.
It's not real. You scared me.
- It's funny.
- Of course it's real.
- It's real?
- Real.
Oh, my--
Are you outta your mind?
You like it?
Well, it's gorgeous, but it's too much.
I-I can't accept it.
You can accept it, and you will.
It's yours. I want you to have it.
What is the Justice of the Peace's name?
Emily Hamilton.
- Oh, my...
- All right, let's file this sucker.
All right. We'll need confirmation
that the ceremony's been performed
within 72 hours, or you will need
to refile.
Congratulations.
- Who said romance is dead?
- I can't take this.
No, not yet you can't.
Well, at least let me try it on.
- Not yet.
- We don't even know if it fits!
- Lisbon, hi.
- Yes!
- Wylie, did we invite you yet?
- No, not yet.
Well, here it is.
Abbott's house, 12:00 Saturday.
But try not to spread it around.
We wanna keep it small.
And I don't wanna hurt
anybody's feelings.
I got you. Is there a gift registry?
- Uh, no gifts.
- Is there a trousseau?
- I don't know. What is that exactly?
- Never mind.
You're coming back
to work, right? Here?
Yeah, I think so.
- Why are you whispering?
- Lisbon, hey.
Someone's trying to reach you.
Oh, my God.
- "Hey, boss."
- "Hi."
- I'll talk to you guys later, okay?
- It is so good to see you guys.
"Right back at ya."
"Well, the news is spreading fast
through the CBI grapevine."
- "It's true, isn't it?"
- It's true.
"Oh, well, we had to call
and say congratulations."
"So, you and Jane, huh?
We always knew."
"We always knew?
I always knew."
How are the kids?
- "Uh, sticky, mostly."
- "The kids are great."
I know it's short notice, but you guys
have gotta come out for the wedding.
It's Saturday.
"Oh, my gosh, of course.
We'd love to."
"It will take a little child-care juggling
but we can swing it."
"You know, worst comes to worst
we'll just bring the little monkeys with us."
- "Keep 'em locked in the rental car."
- "Will not."
- "I'm kidding."
- "Mommy!"
"No, but seriously, we wouldn't
miss it for anything."
"I gotta go. We'll see you soon."
All right, I'll send you the details.
"Great. Take care."
Okay, you guys are all set. It should be
in the mail three to five days.
Thanks.
Excuse me. I need to fill out
a marriage license.
Um, usually there's two of you.
She's running late. I'll get started.
Okay, well, uh, paperwork
is in the end tray.
Just fill that out.
We need both of you here, plus ID.
I see.
Will do, thanks.
City Clerk's office. Please hold.
Thanks for holding.
Yes, how may I help you?
No, ma'am. You can't file online.
Until six, but we're closed
from twelve to one.
You're welcome.
Looks like she stood me up.
Bad omen for a wedding, huh?
Abbott.
Can I run something by you?
Yeah, shoot.
Spot DNA test came back
from the Keller house.
So far, all the recovered body parts
belong to Joe Senior, none for Junior.
They found his gun, but not him.
Oh, damn.
It could be that he was at the epicenter
of the explosion and was vaporized.
But there's a strong possibility
that Keller, A.K.A. Lazarus, is still alive.
Damn.
I let Austin PD know
and we're putting out a BOLO
to all the local hospitals.
Wylie's putting together a KA list
and I'm gonna have agents set up
shop at all of them.
- Well, did you put out a wire just in case--
- He runs for the border, yeah.
All right, well, it seems like
you have everything handled.
I don't know if I should tell
Jane and Lisbon.
- Good question.
- Yeah.
I wouldn't.
We don't have enough to be sure.
And, you know, they're
in a good space right now.
If Lisbon found out
that this case isn't closed
it's likely that she'll cancel the wedding
and join the hunt.
Yeah, there's plenty of time
to tell them after.
But, if he's still alive...
You know, Keller's unpredictable
and Jane did try to kill him.
You know, just in case
why don't we put some bodies
at the wedding
just to keep an eye out.
And it's my house,
so I'll arrange it.
You sure?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's something to keep me busy.
Okay, thanks.
Abbott said it's totally up to you
but that you'd probably prefer
to hold the ceremony outside
and there isn't really
a room inside big enough.
Well, how many people
are we talking about?
Oh! A lotta people are talking about it.
Well, we only invited like 15 people.
Mm... more like 25 or--
I know.
And I don't think people
are waiting for, like a printed invitation...
seeing as there isn't one.
But, hey, on the plus side,
you're popular, girl!
Is that what all these tables are for?
Yeah, Abbott thought they'd be useful.
Don't worry.
He's covering the rental...
and the bartender...
and the caterer.
I guess they're his wedding gift.
I don't know.
Hey, here's a menu.
- There's a caterer?
- Yeah. Yeah, it's fine.
Abbott's loaded.
I mean, look at this house.
I think his wife cleaned up
in the private sector.
Wow.
"Here we are.
Hey, everybody out."
- Hey, Teresa!
- Hey!
- We're here!
- Hey-hey!
T!
Hi! Wow!
- You all came! So many people.
- Yeah, hey.
Sure we came.
We're gonna let our sister down?
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Yeah, hey, guys, say hi to your
Aunt Teresa, all right?
- Hi!
- Who is this?
- Oh, T, this is Lucy, my fiancée.
Lucy, Teresa.
I am so freaked out to meet you at last.
- We're gonna be sisters! Yay!
- Yay!
It's a long story.
- So, you're all here. Welcome to Austin.
- Thanks.
Yeah, it looks like we brought
the weather with us.
FBI!
- Sorry, I'm freaking out right now.
- Yeah, we got that.
- Excuse me?
- You all came.
- Yeah. Already said that, T.
- Let's go in!
- Jason! Jason! Come here!
- Yeah! Okay.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
We have an odd coincidence...
Or not. Maybe.
Austin PD got a missing-person's report
on a local television reporter
named Dan Glover.
The one that interviewed Jane.
Yeah, left work Thursday night,
hasn't been seen since.
The weird thing is, he called here
right around the time he was last seen.
I spoke to him. He said
he wanted to interview Jane again
and I said he was unavailable
because he was getting...
married.
So, you're not even sure
if you spoke to Glover?
No, I mean, I was certain
at the time.
Obviously, it was his caller ID
but now--
So, we have to assume
the killer's alive and looking for Jane.
How many agents are you gonna have
at the wedding?
Four, but now I think
we should probably have more.
At least 10.
We're gonna need eyes
on the front and backyards
and the surrounding neighborhoods.
We should have a chopper on standby
in case we need to pursue.
Yes, sir.
But wouldn't it be wiser
to just postpone the wedding?
Postpone the wedding?
We're the FBI.
There is that upside.
We can use the wedding as bait...
kind of.
I'm gonna go check on that chopper.
Still think we shouldn't tell
Jane and Lisbon?
We're the FBI.
Just like you said, we can handle it.
Abbott.
Hey.
What were you and Cho and Tork
huddled about?
Nothing special.
Nothing special
that's keeping you here
when you could be in Prague
with your lovely wife?
You know, she doesn't need me around.
I...
I get in the way.
You're lying to me.
I won't pursue the point
because you would tell me
if it was something important.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
If-if I thought that it was something
that we couldn't handle.
You know, um...
I've been getting some calls about you
and my bosses wanna know
if you're sticking around.
That's a good question.
All right, well, no pressure.
But if you're going
there is some legal stuff
that we need to handle
to expunge that deal that we made.
The napkin?
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Then I'm building a house, and...
beyond that
I genuinely have no idea.
And I can't do this job forever
but it's gonna be tough to give up.
Yeah, it's hard giving up
making a difference, huh?
No, everyone makes a difference.
- Hard to give up the chase.
- Oh, yeah.
That it is.
So, you, uh, let me know
when you know.
I will.
It has been very good
working with you, Patrick.
You too, Dennis.
I really appreciate your honesty.
I love you for that.
Thank you.
Okay, you got me. I was lying.
There is something
I need to talk to you about.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Nice flowers.
They're centerpieces.
- It's a Sylvan theme.
- Sylvan theme.
All right. Cool, I guess.
How many... people are
actually coming to this thing?
Nobody knows exactly.
Okay.
How did this happen?
This is not what I wanted.
Well, I like the Sylvan theme.
We should've just eloped
like you said.
- What about your family?
- Oh, they wouldn't care.
I just talked to them at the hotel.
They found a minibar.
They're like cavemen
arguing over a dead antelope.
All right, well, uh...
Let's run, huh?
We'll tell nobody, just the judge.
I'll have her meet us
at our little cabin tomorrow morning.
- The cabin?
- Just us.
What, you think the judge
would do that?
Well, sure. I mean, she's driving in
from San Antonio tonight.
Change of venue makes
no difference to her.
- Well, what about the witnesses?
- We'll get someone... Park ranger.
- You know what? Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- It's our life, damn it.
- Yes.
- I love you. Thank you.
- I love you, too.
- Hey, there's a--
- I'm gonna go get my dress
and I'm gonna go to the Airstream.
I'll meet you there.
Well, there's another very good reason
why we should elope, all right?
Keller is apparently still alive
and he's mad at me for some reason.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, so Cho and his people
are gonna stake out this house.
When Keller shows up, they'll nab him.
You were gonna withhold
this information from me?
You were gonna deprive me
of a guilt-free elopement?
- I just told you.
- You almost didn't!
From now on, we need to be
100% honest with each other.
- I agree with you 100%.
- Okay.
- Honesty.
- I am gonna go get my dress.
- Fire up the Airstream.
- You go, girl.
Hi. Judge Hamilton, Patrick Jane.
Uh, there's been a change of venue.
Okay. No problem, Mr. Jane.
If you just text me the exact address
and perhaps a decent motel nearby.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Great. Bye.
We got four agents on the roof
five dressed as catering and valet service
six on the perimeter
and six undercover mobiles
covering the approach roads.
When the guests get here
I'll gather them inside
and explain the situation.
Most of them are law enforcement
so they'll understand.
What is it, Wylie?
Office got a call off the BOLO
from a clerk
at the South Austin Registry Office.
A man with extensive burns
came in yesterday
and pretended to fill out a form.
The clerk thinks
he may have taken a peek
at the marriage-license forms
on her desk.
So that confirms it.
He is coming to the wedding.
Well, we got it covered.
Why are you so anxious, Wylie?
I know all the state forms from
when I used to work downtown.
The marriage-license form
doesn't ask where the wedding is.
- It just asks who the officiant is.
- Well, that's the judge.
Yeah.
- Hey, you.
- Hi.
Wow.
Well, no matter what happens,
from this point on
we have to promise each other that...
we will always
look on the bright side.
I promise.
Me too.
Freeze! Drop the gun!
And see how much better things turn out
when you're honest with me?
Thank you.
Let's do this.
No hard feelings.
Patrick, do you take Teresa to be
your lawful, wedded wife
to have and to hold
in sickness and health
for better or for worse,
till death do you part?
I sure do.
And, you, Teresa, do you take Patrick
to be your lawful, wedded husband
to have and to hold in sickness and health
for better or for worse,
till death do you part?
I do.
Then by the power granted me
by the State of Texas
I declare you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Patrick and Teresa.
"Do you remember"
"The 21st night of September?"
"Love was changing the minds
of pretenders"
- "While chasing the clouds away"
- Who else is gonna hug me? Come on!
"Our hearts were ringing"
"In the key that our souls were singing"
"As we danced in the night, remember"
"How the stars stole the night away?"
"Say, do you remember"
"Dancing in September?"
"Never was a cloudy day"
"My thoughts are with you"
"Holding hands with your heart
to see you"
"Only blue talk and love, remember"
"How we knew love was here to stay?"
"Now, December found the love..."
How you feeling?
I am so happy.
Me too.
There's something I need to tell you.
No, you're--
you're kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
You are?
I am.